GABRIEL GABRIEL GABRIEL
Did you know that bugs don't
have brains like we do?
Then what kind of brains do they have?
Their nervous system acts as their brain,
and it runs all throughout their bodies.
That's why if you remove their head, an
insect can continue living for a bit.
If this can stay alive after its head is
gone, then I wonder where its soul's at.
Yoo-hoo!
Hi, Gabe!
Hi, Alicia.
I'm bored. Want to hang out? Okay.
I wonder where Alicia's soul is.
People aren't like bugs.
Can't live without our heads.
So a person's soul has
to be in their head.
It's got to be somewhere in the brain.
Under her skin, her
skull, deep in her brain.
Her soul's there, hiding.
No way.
Is that you?
Asago?
Oh yeah, you know it. Check it out.
A dork logged us in
and didn't screw it up.
A world of artificial fluctlights.
And every one of them with a soul.
A human soul.
Thank you.
Oh
I believe that the power of the evil
and the evil and the
evil and
the
evil.
Those Flatland Slug
Slurpers won't beat us!
The honor of His Majesty's first
spear will go to the Mountain Goblins!
Let's get to the palace
before the other tribes!
Move out!
Ah!
I am the head of the Commerce
Guild, Your Excellency,
Rengil Gillescobo, at your service.
I be Lil' Pillin, Chief of Orcs.
I am D .I .L., Your Majesty,
head of the Dark Mages Guild.
It is my privilege to serve you.
My 3,000 mages, my heart,
and my body belong to you.
Vixor Ulshasta, head of the Dark Knights.
Before I pledge my
sword, I have a question.
Your Majesty, now that you've returned
after so long, what do you seek?
Blood and terror, fire and
destruction, death and screams.
The western lands flow with the power of
the gods that banished me from the heavens.
But the great gate that protects
those lands shall crumble very soon.
And so I've returned.
This world shall know my
power and tremble before it.
Once the Great Gate falls,
the realm of the humans will
belong to the people of Darkness.
I have but one request of you.
To bring me the Priestess of Light
who resides in the Human Empire.
You have permission to terrorize and
murder any other human, but she is mine.
Go forth, my warriors of Darkness.
Claim your destiny.
Kill!
Drink their blood!
Smash in their skulls
and rip up to pieces!
Rawr!
Hail to the Emperor!
War!
Death to the White Eudes!
I gotta hand it to you, bro.
You got some talent.
You could be a big-time
actor if you wanted.
Please, don't be ridiculous.
A speech was called for and I gave it,
which is a skill you should learn yourself.
Since you are their superior,
they'll be expecting it.
I don't want to give orders or speeches.
I just want to kill some fools.
I've never seen VR be so real, so I figure
I might as well take advantage of it.
I mean, I can friggin' taste this wine!
Just remember, there's
no pain absorber here.
If you get cut, it'll bleed and hurt. Bad.
I know.
That's what makes this great.
That you, Captain? Yeah.
Good timing.
We got back to main control just now.
Wanted to make sure your
dive didn't have issues.
Thank you.
So far, our first day here went well.
The phenomenon of accelerated time
takes a bit of getting used to.
Other than that, everything's going
as planned, so I'm not complaining.
We should have these units equipped
and ready in two days, our time.
Then we'll launch the
attack on the Human Empire.
Sweet!
Alright, so here's what to do.
Once you have Alice, get her back to
that terminal and bring up the menu.
There will be an option there to eject
her light cube to the main control room.
Click on that, and Alice's
light cube's as good as ours.
Oh, and while you're there,
there's something you and that
dumbass Vassago should keep in mind.
What?!
Since we don't have access
to admin privileges,
we don't have the luxury of resetting. So,
if you gents end up getting killed,
I won't be able to log you back
in with those super-user accounts.
The best I can do is send
you back as low-level grunts.
Got it.
We'll be careful.
What's the SDF up to?
Nothing at the moment.
I bet they're so freaked out, they
don't even know you dove in there.
Good.
I guess that's it for now.
Hopefully, the next time you
hear from me, we'll have Alice.
Roger that. Good luck.
God, I hate that asswipe.
I was thinking, maybe I'll head downtown
and, you know, blow off a little steam.
No, I'd prefer it if you didn't.
Once the op's over, you can
have a night all to yourself.
All right, standing down
on the chicks and murder.
I'll hit the sack and
dream about him instead.
What are you doing here?
I shall be your company tonight,
if it pleases your majesty.
Well.
And by whose order no one my duty
is to indulge your whims, sire?
All right then!
If you please!
Who put you up to this?
My own volition!
Then who's your commanding officer?
No one!
Still, you must Have a
reason for your treachery?
Did you do it for money or did
someone promise You status?
For the good of the land?
Really?
If war breaks out it will set
History back hundreds of years?
We cannot revert to the old ways where
the Powerless suffered under oppression?
Ah, there it is, just like that day.
Oh, my God.
I don't know.
I just saw Alicia's soul.
And for a second there, I could
see what her soul was seeing, too.
A human soul.
I want to see more of what it showed me.
I can't wait to see it again.
I love you so much, my lord.
That was incredible.
What a glorious experience.
Even though our flux
lights are in separate
light cubes they connected
through the stl So
when she died maybe the release of quantum
data flowed back to me
by way of that connection
What am I doing who
cares about the how of it
I've experimented with so
many people since Alicia,
and finally, I've experienced
the phenomenon again, here.
If that's what an average AI soul is
like, Alice's should be extraordinary.
Alice, your soul will be
sweet, and I shall relish it.
My lord, all preparations are complete.
We are ready to launch the
assault whenever it pleases you.
Good.
The life of the Eastern Gate,
which has divided the Human Empire and
the Land of Darkness since creation,
will expire soon.
The Five Tribes are excited
about the prospect of war
and the bounty of resources
the Human Empire contains.
And yet, each Integrity Knight is worth
a thousand of our warriors in battle.
The edge we have in our numbers
shall be whittled down in no time.
Beating them may be possible,
but by the time we do, we will
have suffered severe losses.
If that's true, it will lead to an
imbalance of power among the tribes.
The Council of Ten will be powerless,
and the treaty among the five
tribes will be rescinded.
If that happens, it will become
another age of blood and iron.
That cannot come to pass.
Our only hope is to make
peace with the human empire.
I must speak with Bercoli.
I am certain he would agree
to our request for peace.
But first, I must kill the
one who stands in the way.
Emperor Vector.
By the way, last night I discovered
an intruder in my chamber.
They had a dagger hidden in their hair.
Fear not, I won't condemn whoever
sent the assassin after me.
If you wish to have more power, there is
nothing wrong using treachery to obtain it.
And if you desire the throne, feel
free to attack me however you wish.
With that said,
if you decide to embark on such a gamble,
know that the consequences
will be most severe.
For example, this traitor.
We must have peace for the sake of all.
That sounds so hypocritical,
especially coming from the
commander of the Dark Knights.
It is admirable.
And so are you.
Oh, my lord, that is why I
love you and always will.
The poison coursing
through you is so potent,
it can kill a land dragon with a life
of over 30,000 in less than an hour.
And compared to your stamina and total
life, you'll be dead in about three minutes.
My dear, they won't stop me.
Oh, my God.
Nothing, a black void, does
this man not know life?
He knows nothing of the radiance
of life, of love, of the soul.
That's why he seeks other souls.
No matter how powerful
my incarnate ability was,
this man cannot be defeated by
a weapon of murderous intent.
He has a soul, but it is dead.
I'm so sorry, Lipia.
The troops who lost their
commanders shall appoint
whoever is the next
highest rank to lead them.
We will begin the assault as
planned one hour from now.
Long live Vecta, the Emperor!
Hmph.
If you're alone, you'll be
able to live with one person.
I don't want anyone to love you.
It's your scent, it's your story.
I am the body of love.
That's my dream!
My dream!
That's just?
There it is, the Eastern Gate.
Hold here, Amayori.
Destroyed at the last stage.
We are out of time.
Next time, Kaisen Siune.